diamondnexus.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy

#### Our commitment to privacy:

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

#### The way we use our information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Any user submitting an email addresses while in the process of entering contests or requests of promotional materials will be automatically enrolled in our email marketing program. All individuals who purchase will be enrolled in our email marketing program. Users are free to opt-out of our email marketing program at any time by selecting unsubscribe at the bottom of any email. Unsubscribing will permanently remove the user from email marketing unless that user enters another contest or requests promotional materials again at a future date. Users requesting catalogs will be enrolled to receive physical mailings alerting them to future sales & promotions. Any user who does not wish to receive physical mailings can contact customer service to be removed from these mailing lists.

#### Our commitment to data security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### Our commitment to children's policy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### How can you access or correct your information:

You can access all the personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by setting up an account and logging in with your personal private password. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that shows the error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

#### Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of code that are stored on your web-browser. They contain basic information about your online activities. Cookies do not contain any information that identifies who you are. We use cookies to deliver our ads, measure activities on our website, track visits to our site, and track website performance. This information is then used to improve the usability of DiamondNexus.com and deliver a better user experience for all visitors. An example of how we use cookies is to launch two layouts of a page and track which one has a longer visit duration and results in more sales. It must be stressed again that cookies contain no information that would enable DiamondNexus to identify who you are.

You are always free to disallow cookies if your browser has this feature. Disabling cookies will however reduce the features of DiamondNexus.com and many other websites you visit.

#### Google Analytics

DiamondNexus uses Google Analytics to track website performance. Google Analytics uses cookies to gather basic information about your gender, web interests, and browsing behavior. This information will in no way allow Google or DiamondNexus to identify you individually. If you create an account with DiamondNexus, your personal contact information will never be given to Google.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics data gathering on [this page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

#### European Privacy Rights & Personal Data Protection

For individuals who reside in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) you are afforded data protection under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Under the GDPR Diamond Nexus gives you the following rights and will adhere to all of the following requests regarding your data: 

  * **Request a copy of and/or changes to your data:** As a user in the EEA you can request a copy of all personal data that Diamond Nexus has on file. You can also request that we change any incorrect or incomplete data on file.
  * **Request deletion of all data:** You have the right to request that select pieces or the entirety of your personal data is removed from all Diamond Nexus databases.
  * **Request cessation of personal data processing:** At any point you can request that Diamond Nexus ceases processing all or portions of your data. 

Exercising these rights & requests

To exercise your rights and make any of the aforementioned requests please contact Diamond Nexus at [customerservice@diamondnexus.com](mailto:customerservice@diamondnexus.com?subject=European%20Privacy%20Rights) or send mail to:

Data Processing Requests  
c/o Diamond Nexus  
5050 W. Ashland Way  
Franklin, WI 53132

Complaints

You have the right to file a complaint regarding Diamond Nexus’ usage of your personal data or the terms of this privacy policy by sending an email to [customerservice@diamondnexus.com](mailto:customerservice@diamondnexus.com?subject=European%20Privacy%20Rights%20Complaint). We will reply to your complaint as quickly as possible

If your complaint is not resolved and you are located in the EEA, the GDPR gives you the right to contact your local data [protection authority.](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm)
